klip.com 2011-10-28

# 

**Klip Privacy Policy**

We respects your privacy and will not  share your private information with people you don't choose to share it with.

Klip's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using Klip applications or accessing [www.klip.com](http://www.klip.com/).

By using Klip applications or accessing our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us at [privacy@klip.com](mailto:privacy@klip.com) _._

**The Information We Collect**

When you launch a Klip application you provide us with four types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us; locational use information collected by us as you interact with our services; usage information that is collected by our servers as you use our applications; and information related to third party services that you would like to access through our applications and services.

When you register with Klip, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, username, your email address and a photo representation ("avatar") and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you launch or interact with a Klip application, we collect your device type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users. In addition, we use the unique Device ID ("UUID") that vendors such as Apple and Android licensees makes available for each  device in order to authenticate the user session. This UUID functions similarly to a persistent cookie to make it possible to authenticate the user without the need for a password. You can disassociate a UUID from a user account at any time by emailing us at [privacy@klip.com](mailto:privacy@klip.com) _._

When you use Klip applications, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior videos or messages you have posted or easily see the list of people you follow. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

You post User Content through Klip applications at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post with Klip will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained in Klip applications. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived form or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Klip applications is a violation of the Klip Terms of Service and should be reported to [privacy@klip.com](mailto:privacy@klip.com).

If you choose to use our invitation service, we may ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as the receipient's email address and we will automatically send a one-time email or instant message inviting him or her to visit the site or to download our application. Klip stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a new  connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. The person you invited may contact us at [privacy@klip.com](mailto:privacy@tapulous.com) to request that we remove this information from our databases.

Klip may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of Klip applications through the operation of the service in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.By using Klip, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

**Third Party Services Accessed by Klip**

You can configure certain third party services to be accessed by Klip applications and services. When you do so, we will store your access credentials to such third party services in a secure manner; we may temporarily cache your list of contacts from these services; and we will store messages, videos, and other content created using our applications that are delivered to such third party services. We do this to improve the performance and experience of these services (such as, adding videos and location information not available in the third party services).

**Use of Information Obtained by Klip**

When you register with Klip, you create your own profile.

Your name, username and avatar (but not email address) are displayed to other Klip users to enable you to connect with people on Klip. We expect that you will use the name which you are most commonly known by.  We may occasionally use your username or email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by Klip that we think you may find valuable.

Your profile can be shared across all of the applications in the Klip portfolio. As a previously registered user, when you download and access a new Klip application, your user profile is automatically incorporated into that new application. 

Klip may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a person you follow posts a new video, you may receive an email or other notification alerting you to that fact. These announcements may also relate to new product launches or other relevant information about Klip and the services we provide.

Klip may use information in your profile or related to your activities on Klip applications in order to personalize the application experience for you. Klip may also share information such as user trends and application downloads in aggregate to third parties without identifying you as an individual.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**

Klip is about users sharing information with others. 

We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) necessary for business operations (e.g., emailing you through a third party server), 2) legally required or when we choose to collaborate with a law enforcement agency in the investigation of a possible crime, 3) permitted by you.

If the ownership of  Klip, Inc. were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

**Changing or Removing Information**

Klip users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Klip account may do so by emailing us at [privacy@klip.com](mailto:privacy@tapulous.com). Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of Klip.

Klip services and applications have communication features that allow you to share information with other individuals on Klip, however, you generally cannot remove such communications.

**Security**

Klip takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server or are hosted by a third party cloud service provider such as Amazon. Klip does not run and cannot guarantee the security of  third party cloud service providers. If you have any questions about the security of Klip applications, please contact us at [privacy@klip.com](mailto:privacy@klip.com).

**Children**

Klip does not knowingly collect or retain personal information about persons under 13 years of age.  Any person who provides their personal information to Klip through its Services must be 13 years of age or older.  If we learn that personal information of persons under the age of 13 years has been collected on one of our Services we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.  

If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained a Service account, then you may alert us at  ** _privacy@klip.com_**  and request that we delete that child's personal information from our systems.  

**International Users**

The Services are currently hosted in the United States.  If you visit any of the Services from other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from laws of the United States, you acknowledge that you are transferring personal information outside of those jurisdictions to the United States for the uses identified above and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  By providing your personal information on any of the Services you consent to that transfer.  

**Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions**

Your use of Klip, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Contacting Klip**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@klip.com](mailto:privacy@tapulous.com).
